<?xml version="1.0"?>
<list>
    <disease>
        <name>E. coli</name>
        <description>A coliform, rod-shaped bacterium, Escherichia coli are commonly found in the gut.</description>
        <hint>Many strains of E. coli are part of the gut's normal microbiota. It's probably okay to ignore it.</hint>
        <location>small intestine</location>
        <question>It's just normal E. coli. Enter "okay" to continue.</question>
        <correctAnswer>okay</correctAnswer>
        <points>50</points>
    </disease>
    <disease>
        <name>Salmonella</name>
        <description>A capsular bacterium that uses its many flagella to travel from place to place, Salmonella targets the stomach.</description>
        <hint>It looks like this pathogen is able to produce energy regardless of its surroundings. Perhaps a general attack can do the trick.</hint>
        <location>stomach</location>
        <question>Salmonella is wreaking havoc. A pyrrhic victory is still a victory. Call the help of which self-sacrificing cell?</question>
        <correctAnswer>NK cells</correctAnswer>
        <points>70</points>
    </disease>
    <disease>
        <name>C. difficile</name>
        <description>Clostridiodes difficile, a motile, drumstick-shaped bacteria.</description>
        <hint>C. difficile is spore-forming. Better not take too long fighting it.</hint>
        <location>colon</location>
        <question>This requires immediate action. Which cells of the innate immune system should be used?</question>
        <correctAnswer>white blood cells</correctAnswer>
        <points>50</points>
    </disease>
    <disease>
        <name>Chlamydia psittaci</name>
        <description>Psittaci, a zoonotic bacterium responsible for parrot fever, presents chiefly as an atypical pneumonia that can lead to a coma.</description>
        <hint>It looks like it might be susceptible to bacteriophages.</hint>
        <location>lungs</location>
        <question>This typically requires tetracyclines. In the mean time, which cells should take action?</question>
        <correctAnswer>Macrophage</correctAnswer>
    </disease>
    <disease>
        <name>Fungal Meningitis</name>
        <description>An altered state of mind, nausea clouding your head.  When did the lights become so intense?  The spore-forming fungal meningitis blends into the pellucid cerebrospinal fluid as it finishes its travel from the lungs.</description>
        <hint>The fungus boasts a mortality rate of 10-20% amongst its afflicted. Fortunately, it's not transmissible between humans. It'll take a while to defeat this.</hint>
        <location>brain</location>
        <question>The blood-brain barrier makes this especially tricky. Which cells should be used to extirpate the fungal fury?</question>
        <correctAnswer>B cells</correctAnswer>
        <points>50</points>
    </disease>
    <disease>
        <name>Prion</name>
        <description>The harbinger of many transmissible neurodegenerative diseases (e.g., Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease, Chronic Wasting Disease, spongiform encephalopathy), prions denature the brain's proteins, invariably leading to death.</description>
        <hint>Prions are durable, proteinaceous extremophiles. Beyond the host's life, these proteins remain virulent. Death is ineluctable.</hint>
        <location>brain</location>
        <question>Nothing can be done. Accept death and make amends. Play again?</question>
        <correctAnswer>Yes</correctAnswer>
        <points>100</points>
    </disease>
</list>